我们用数学算过了
The math is all there.
-这不可能  -的确可能
- It's not real. - Yes, it is.
好吧  听着
Yeah... uh, look.
从科学角度上来说  单凭一人之力
It is scientifically impossible
Tip a cow over是指在牛站着睡觉的时候悄悄走到旁边
将其推倒取乐的一种活动
不可能从侧面将牛推倒
for a person to tip a cow.
就连你这个虎背熊腰的女汉子
Even you, with your stocky build and lumberjack shoulders,
也不可能做到
you couldn't do it.
太可怕了  你为什么要把牛推到
It's horrible. Why would you push a cow over?
它们多神圣啊
They're sacred.
少来了
Oh, stop it.
我都见你吃过不下一百万个牛肉汉堡了
I've seen you eat, like, a million hamburgers.
动物可以集神圣和美味于一身
Hey, an animal can be both sacred and delicious.
告诉你们  我的确把牛推倒过
Look, I'm telling you I've done it, okay?
我清楚地记得牛先是站着的
I clearly remember the cow standing up
然后就倒到一侧了
and then the cow on its side.
你是不是喝醉了
Were you drunk?
我当时是内布拉斯加州的16岁少女  你觉得呢
I was 16 in Nebraska. What do you think?
我觉得你才是倒下的那个
I think you're the one who fell over.
怪不得当时天空也也倒在一侧
That would explain why the sky was also on its side.
霍华德  "推牛倒"是真的还是假的
Howard. Cow tipping: real or not?
我觉得是  假的
I'm gonna say... not.
因为我曾试过在我妈打鼾时让她翻身
That's just based on me trying to roll my mom over
可死都推不动她
when she's snoring.
说到大块的肉
Speaking of that big side of beef,
她邀请你们去她家过感恩节
uh, she's invited all of you to Thanksgiving at her house.
有人跟我说  赤裸裸地拒绝别人的邀请
You know, I've been told that a bald refusal
是很无礼的
of an invitation is rude
所以必须编造一个礼貌的借口来回绝
and one must instead offer up a polite excuse, so...
我也很想去  但不幸的是
I'd love to go, but, unfortunately,
那听起来很可怕
that sounds awful.
去嘛  一点都不可怕
Come on, it'll be fun.
我们其实打算在这里过
Uh, we were actually gonna do it here.
拜托啦  伯纳黛特的妈妈不在家
Please? Bernadette's bringing her dad
所以她会带她爸来
'cause her mom's out of town,
可我跟他爸总是话不投机
and I never have anything to say to that guy.
既然你都这么说了  我也想帮你
Oh, since you put it that way, I'd love to go,
但那听起来更可怕了
but that sounds even more awful.
其实不用一天都听
It'd actually be nice to not hear
谢尔顿抱怨我的厨艺挺好的
Sheldon complain about my cooking all day.
什么  不好意思
Yo... uh, excuse me,
但每年你的菜都做得难吃
but every year you prepare a terrible meal
我每年都批评你的厨艺
and every year I criticize it.
难道我们的传统对你来说毫无意义吗
Do our traditions mean nothing to you?
-我想去  -我也是
- I want to go. - Yeah, me, too.
-我也去  -谢尔顿
- I'm in. - Sheldon.
好吧  我去
Ugh, fine, I'll go.
但如果菜都很好吃  那感恩节就被毁了
But if her food is delicious, Thanksgiving is ruined,
这笔账算你的
and it's on you.
生活大爆炸
第七季  第九集
我们真的要去沃罗威茨夫人家吃饭吗
Do we really have to go to Mrs. Wolowitz's house?
是的
We do.
我希望你的行为举止要得当
And I expect you to be on your best behavior.
现在我了解非洲黑奴当时的感受了
Now I know how the African slaves felt.
被人强行从自己家园拖出
Being dragged from their homes
沦为受白人控制和使唤的劳力
to labor under the yoke of the white man.
你真的要把
Are you honestly comparing
去沃罗威茨妈妈家吃饭
Thanksgiving dinner at Wolowitz's mom's
和人类历史上最大的悲剧之一
with one of the greatest tragedies
这两件事相提并论吗
in the history of mankind?
是的
Yes.
谢尔顿  不管在哪里都可以过个开心的感恩节
Sheldon, you can have a nice Thanksgiving anywhere.
我就在维加斯试过
I spent one in Vegas.
是吗
You did?
对啊  当时我在跟扎克约会
Yeah, back when I was dating Zack.
那个感恩节比我想象中有趣多了
It was actually more fun than I thought.
我们先去赌博  然后去了一家低档的婚礼教堂
We gambled, we went to one of those cheesy wedding chapels,
我们还吃了一顿超美味的火鸡大餐
we had a really good turkey dinner.
真的想不到这么好吃  因为我们是在脱衣舞俱乐部
Which was surprising, since we were at a strip club.
慢着  你们俩还去教堂了吗
Wait, you went to a chapel?
-是啊  -去干嘛
- Yeah. - Why?
我们不过是办了一场假婚礼
We had one of those silly fake weddings.
拉斯维加斯办理结婚无需繁琐的手续
只要新郎新娘两个人说"我愿意"就可以
佩妮
Penny...
你知道那是真结婚  对吧
you know those are real, right?
不  是假结婚
No, they're not.
是真的
Yeah, they are.
是假的
No, they're not.
是真的
Yeah, they are.
-他说得对  -是真的
- He's right. - They're real.
但那看上去不像真的呀
But it... didn't seem real.
我问你个问题
Let me ask you a question.
有没可能  当时你眼中的拉斯维加斯是倒在一侧的呢
At any point, was Las Vegas on its side?
-爸爸  -乖宝贝
- Hi, Dad. - Hi, honey.
你还给大家买了啤酒啊
Oh, you brought beer for everybody.
好吧  没错  人人都有份
Uh, okay, yeah, it's for everybody.
我真是只想今天安静地在家待着
I really just wanted to have a nice, quiet day at home
看看比赛
and watch the game.
你在这里也能安静待着看比赛啊
You can have a quiet day and watch the game here.
霍华德  那药不管用
Howard, the medicine's not working!
你刚吃了没多久
You just took it.
至少等它先到达你第一个胃再说
At least let it reach your first stomach!
迈克  来了啊
Hey, Mike.
-我来帮你拿吧  -谢谢
- Let me help you out, there. - Thanks.
你妈妈怎么了
What's wrong with your mom?
她的痛风加重了
Oh, her gout's flaring up.
看来一天一个苹果派
Turns out an apple pie a day
并不能让你远离疾病
does not keep the doctor away.
为什么我的小脚趾这么疼呢
How can one little toe hurt so bad?
或许是因为那只小脚趾
Maybe because that little piggy
被你的庞大的身躯压碎了
is being crushed by the barn!
她很快就会安静下来
She should quiet down soon.
我给她的止痛药足以让一头...
I gave her enough pain meds to choke a...
让她安静下来
well, her.
我们得开始做饭了
I guess we're gonna have to do all the cooking.
我有个更好的主意
I have a better idea.
如果你想让我一个人干所有的活
If you think you're gonna make me do all this by myself,
那绝对不行
you're crazy.
我是想让拉杰一个人干所有的活
I was gonna make Raj do it all by himself.
那真是个好主意
Oh, well, that's a great idea.
路上没车  真是一帆风顺啊
No traffic, we're sailing.
是啊
Yes.
好像我们在船上一样
Like we're on a ship.
一艘从非洲到美国的船
Coming from Africa to America.
谢尔顿  这样做太不恰当了
Sheldon, that's completely inappropriate.
你不能一直将自己比作奴隶
You can't keep comparing yourself to a slave.
是的  艾米小姐
Yes, Miss Amy.
真不敢相信你居然跟那个傻蛋结婚了
I can't believe you're married to that idiot.
别说了行吗  我们只是闹着玩的
Ugh, would you stop? We just did it as a goof.
不管是不是闹着玩  你们都是真结婚了
Well, a goof or not, you're actually married.
-你得解决这件事  -我会的
- You need to get this taken care of. - I will.
你干嘛在这件事上小题大作
Why are you making this such a big deal?
我知道原因
Oh, oh, oh, I have a reason.
可能是因为你愿意嫁给扎克
It could be because you said yes to marrying Zack,
而每次莱纳德向你求婚时
but every time Leonard's proposed,
你总是拒绝他
he's gotten a resounding no.
我一下子就想到这个答案了
Yeah, that's just off the top of my head.
那我该怎么办
So how do I undo this?
我希望你能解除婚约
I'm hoping you can get an annulment.
就好像这事从来没发生过
It's just like it never happened.
好啊  那我应该怎么做
Great, well, what do I have to do?
从法律上说  解除婚约
It says here you can get an annulment
必须满足一下任何一个条件
if any of the following conditions are met.
"婚后  两人从未圆房"
"Were you unable to consummate the marriage?"
佩妮是欲女  下一条
Penny? Next.
"两人间存在欺骗  重婚
"Is there any evidence of fraud, bigamy,
缺乏谅解"
want of understanding?"
到底什么是"缺乏谅解[理解力]"
"Want of understanding?" What does that even mean?
叮叮叮  说的就是你
Ding, ding, ding. We have a winner.
谢谢你救我于水火之中
Thanks for saving the day.
不用谢
Ah, no problem.
美国的第一个感恩节是印第安人与新移民第一次齐聚感谢上天赐予
并感谢印第安人曾在危急的时刻送来食物和帮助他们
没有印第安人[印度人]献上美食
It wouldn't be Thanksgiving
就不算是真正的感恩节
without an Indian providing the food.
你妈妈把植物奶油放哪里了
Uh, now, where does your mom keep the Crisco?
我不知道
Um, I don't know.
大概是塞在她脸颊的肥肉里了
Probably in a wad in her cheek.
我在这里帮拉杰
I'll help Raj in here.
你出去陪我爸爸好吗
Why don't you go keep my dad company?
他可不想我陪他
Oh, he doesn't want me in there.
我在他眼中是  睡了他乖女儿的讨厌鬼
I'm the creepy little guy who has sex with his daughter.
-别傻了  他喜欢你  -真的吗
- Don't be silly, he loves you. - Does he?
-好吧  至少他关心你啊  -真的吗
- Okay, he cares about you a lot. - Really?
老娘不也经常为你做牛做马  快滚出去
I do crap for you all the time. Get out there.
你太太和孙子们一起待在亚利桑那吗
So your wife's in Arizona with the grandkids?
我妈妈也去过亚利桑那州
You know, my mom's been to...Arizona.
她骑着一头骡子穿越大峡谷
She rode one of those mules down in the Grand Canyon.
最后为了让骡子落个安乐死  人们把它射死了
Long story short, they had to shoot it.
因为我妈实在太胖了
'Cause she's so fat.
您慢慢笑  我去开门
I'll get the door while you finish laughing.
大家好
Hey, guys.
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving.
闻起来真香啊
It smells wonderful.
是谁在厨房做苦力
Is anyone slaving away in the kitchen?
-因为我也...  -谢尔顿
- Because I, too, know... - Sheldon.
给你  谢谢你邀请我们
Here. Thank you for having us.
-你怎么了  -她在生我的气
- What's with you? - Oh, she's mad at me
因为她刚发现她和扎克结婚了
because she just found out she's married to Zack.
真的吗
Really?
那个和她约会过的傻蛋吗
That dumb-ass she used to date?
这也太搞笑了
That's hysterical.
亏我还为在车里打开了这酒而自责
I can't believe I felt bad for opening this in the car.
-你俩要帮忙吗  -好呀
- You need any help? - Uh, yeah,
你能拿一下上面的酱汁碗吗
can you, uh, reach that, uh, gravy boat up there?
-没问题  -太好了
- Uh, sure. - Great.
至少你俩还有人能够得着
That makes one of you.
我们任务重大  时间却很紧迫
Okay, we have a lot to do and not much time to do it.
伯纳黛特  你负责玉米  肉酱汁和红薯
Bernadette, you're on corn, gravy and yam detail.
艾米  你负责面包卷  蔓越莓
Amy, you're on rolls, cranberries
并且确保不让伯纳黛特靠近棉花糖
and making sure Bernadette stays away from the marshmallows.
没错  我看见你偷吃了
That's right, I see you.
如果有问题要问
Okay, if you have any questions,
我就在这里  专心地给烤肉刷油
I'll be over here basting my ass off.
集中注意力是关键
Focus is key.
你们知道佩妮和扎克三年前就结婚了吗
Did you guys know Penny married Zack three years ago?
-什么  -啥
- What? - Wha...?
你打过橄榄球吗
You ever play football?
大学时玩过一点
A little in college.
-你呢  -没玩过
- You? - No.
不过我曾经作为球  被人在走廊阻截过一次
But I did get tackled in the hallway once.
整个学校欢声雷动啊
The whole school cheered.
我找到了你和扎克
Hey, I found the, uh, court papers
需要填写的法庭文件
that you and Zack need to fill out.
-等我回家就打印出来  -行
- I'll print them when we get home. - Fine.
然后我们就可以彻底忘掉这事了
And we can just put this whole thing behind us.
-你有完没完  -怎么了
- Are you done? - What?
我知道  我做错了
Look, I get it, I screwed up.
难道今天剩下的时间  你都要提起这件事吗
Is this all we're gonna talk about the rest of the day?
你对我凶什么呀
Why are you mad at me?
明明是你做了蠢事
You're the one that did the stupid thing.
而我只是帮你解决而已
I'm just trying to fix it.
我需要呼吸点新鲜空气
I need some air.
那个...佩妮
Well... Penny.
我虽然完全不了解女人
Now, I don't know the first thing about women,
但我要是你  我就不会跟出去
but I would not follow her.
听瘦高个的话没错
Listen to Stretch.
怎么成了我的错了
How am I the bad guy?
是她乱嫁人  我是受害者好吗
She's the one who married someone else. I'm the victim.
扎克才是受害者吧
Sounds like Zack's the victim.
你睡了人家老婆
You're sleeping with his wife.
我的婚姻35年来一直幸福和睦
I've kept my marriage together for 35 years.
我能给点建议吗
Can I weigh in here?
好呀
Sure.
我正在看比赛呢  闭嘴
I'm trying to watch the game. Shut up.
怎么会错过第一次进攻呢
How do you not make a first down there?
人家用了五个后卫  他们还敢传球
They passed against a nickel defense.
应该采取摆脱拦截才对
They should have run it off-tackle.
你怎么会看球
How the hell do you know that?
我爸爱死橄榄球了
My father loved football.
他总是强迫我一起看
He always made me watch it
不看完不准做作业
before I was allowed to do my homework.
你高兴了吧  我刚打电话给扎克了
Well, you'll be happy to know I just spoke to Zack
他会签那些文件的
and he's willing to sign the court papers.
他马上就过来
He's on his way here now.
-等等  你居然让他来这  -是呀
- Wait, you invited him here? - Yeah.
我准备再次发表建议了
I'm getting ready to weigh in again.
过来
Come on.
你觉得他们现在应该怎么做
What do you think they ought to do now?
我会快速斜向往球场内出发  扔球给外接手
I would throw a quick slant to a wideout,
因为防守线卫似乎要向传球员突袭了
given that the defense is showing blitz.
我最喜欢薄饼卷了
Oh, I love a good blitz,
尤其是加酸奶油的那种
especially with sour cream.
懂我笑点吗
Get it?
因为这两者音很近啊
'Cause it sounds like "Blintz."
刚有人说"薄饼卷"吗
Did someone say "Blintz"?!
我不明白你为什么非得今天把他叫来
I just don't understand why you invited him here today.
因为你唠叨个没完
Because you wouldn't shut up about it.
我打给他时  他反正也没事干
When I called him, he had nothing to do,
所以我就想...
so I just thought it would...
两位  我在里面做饭呢
Hey, guys, I'm trying to cook in here.
抱歉  我们会小点声的
Oh, sorry. We'll keep it down.
不  大声点
No, no, speak up.
我要用搅拌器了
I'm about to use the blender,
可我一句也不想漏掉
and I don't want to miss anything.
你要多准备一人份的食物了
Well, you might have to cook for one more
因为她邀请了扎克过来
because she invited Zack.
-什么  -哇哦
- What? - Ooh!
我的天
My, my.
故事发展如同我的肉汁  越加复杂[浓厚]了
The plot, like my gravy, thickens.
我不喜欢你妈的卫生间
I don't care for your mother's bathroom.
不管你面朝哪边尿尿
There's not an angle to do one's business
都有一个小丑雕像瞪着你
without a clown figurine staring at you.
所以我才坐着尿
That's why I sit.
没错  所以你才不爷们
Yeah, that's why.
你还记得达拉斯下大雪的
You remember the Thanksgiving game
那次感恩节比赛吗
when it snowed in Dallas?
1993年
1993--
里昂·莱特在最后几秒犯了错
Leon Lett blew the game in the final seconds
海豚队取得了胜利
and the Dolphins emerged victorious.
于是我终于能做我的微积分题了
Then I finally got to do my calculus.
我当时气疯了  差点没一枪崩了电视
I was so pissed, I wanted to shoot my TV.
我爸也是
So was my dad.
他真的开了枪
And then he did.
-有人还要啤酒吗  -我要
- Anyone need a beer?-  Yeah.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
你爸爸还住在德克萨斯吗
So, does your dad still live in Texas?
不  我十四岁时他就死了
No. He died when I was 14.
真是太遗憾了
I'm sorry to hear that.
本地酒店的老板也很遗憾
So was the man who owned the local liquor store.
他泣不成声  痛哭流涕
He cried and cried.
啤酒来了
Here you go.
谢谢
Oh, thanks.
既然你爸在你十四岁就过世了
So, if your dad died when you were 14,
你肯定没机会和他一起喝啤酒吧
you were never old enough to have a beer with the man.
是的  先生
No, sir.
我高中毕业时他想跟我喝一罐
He did try to give me one for my high school graduation,
但我才11岁  我妈妈说不行
but I was 11 and my mom said no.
那你就跟我喝一罐吧
Well, you're having one with me.
好的
All right.
敬你的父亲
To your dad.
我也从来没和我爸喝过啤酒
I never had a beer with my dad, either.
能别插嘴吗  我们喝得正欢呢
Do you mind? We're having a moment here.
真不敢相信佩妮嫁给了扎克
I can't believe Penny's married to Zack.
不知道她看上他哪一点
Wonder what she saw in that guy.
不知道
I don't know.
他可爱  高大  英俊
He's sweet, he's tall, handsome.
他有宽阔的肩膀  浓密的头发
Broad shoulders, good hair.
不知道她看上莱纳德哪一点
Wonder what she sees in Leonard.
外面情况如何
How's it going out there?
谢尔顿和你爸把酒言欢
Sheldon and your dad are bonding
完全无视我的存在
and completely ignoring me.
我知道你的感受
I know how you feel.
他买了智能吸尘器后  无视了我一周
Sheldon ignored me for a week when he got that Roomba vacuum.
趁他不注意的时候  我踢了那玩意一脚
I kick it when he's not looking.
他们在做什么
What are they doing?
喝啤酒  看橄榄球比赛
They're drinking beer and watching football.
你就和他们一起呗
So why don't do that with them.
他们不要我
They don't want me.
什么意思
What do you mean?
谢尔顿开始诉说他的父亲已经不在人世了
Well, Sheldon started talking about how his dad isn't alive anymore,
在他们碰杯时  我试图告诉他们
and they were toasting, and I tried to tell them about
我父亲抛弃我们时  我有多难过
how sad I was when my dad abandoned...
扎克到了
Zack's here!
搅拌肉汁
Stir the gravy.
对不起  我真的很想听你有多难过
Sorry. I really want to hear how sad you are.
五到十分钟后  我就会回来了
I'll be back in like five, ten minutes.
抱歉今天过节  她还让你过来
Sorry she made you come over here on a holiday.
没关系  反正我也没安排
It's all right. I didn't have anything going on.
而且  佩妮说我们结婚了
Plus, Penny told me we're married,
感恩节就是要和家人一起
and Thanksgiving's a time to be with family.
非常好
Yeah, okay, great.
咱们速战速决吧
Can we just get this over with?
好  在这里和这里签名
Yeah, uh, you guys have to sign here and here.
星期一  我们会提出无效申请
On Monday, we'll file for the annulment,
这段婚姻就结束了
and this "Marriage" will be over.
好了
Okay.
我不确定我是否想签这份文件
I don't know if I want to sign it.
你为什么不想签
Why won't you sign it?
我只是觉得分手对孩子影响不好
I just think splitting up can be rough on kids.
我们没有孩子
We don't have any kids.
你确定吗  你也是
Are you sure? 'Cause you didn't know
今早才知道我们结婚了
we were married until this morning.
扎克  拜托
Okay, look, Zack, come on.
我们都知道那场婚礼不是真的
You know neither of us thought this was real.
主婚人是山寨猫王
I mean, we were married by an Elvis impersonator.
当然是山寨的了
Of course it was an impersonator.
真的猫王我们请不起好吧
We could never afford a real Elvis.
你居然嫁给他  不嫁给我
You married him instead of me?
真有眼光
Good call.
快签字
Sign the papers.
慢着  算了
Hang on. You know what?
你一整天都是一副欠揍的态度
You have been a jerk about this all day.
你总是这样  每次我犯了错
You always do this-- whenever I mess up,
你就在旁边数落我  让我感觉更难受
you're right there to make me feel even worse about it.
才不是
That is not true.
我们本可以等到周一  再签文件
Yeah, we could've waited till Monday, signed the papers,
这事就算过去了
this all would have been over.
是你把他叫过来的
You're the one who invited him here.
你又来了
Oh, there you go again--
又开始当着我的面数落我的错误
just another mistake you're throwing in my face.
这可不好  兄弟
Not cool, bro.
我开始觉得
I'm starting to think
我不想我老婆跟你这种人约会
you're not the kind of guy I want dating my wife.
好吧
Yeah, well,
她做你老婆的时间不会很久了
she's not gonna be your wife for long.
不是吧  你快死了吗
Oh, no. Are you dying?
快了  快签字吧
I'm about to. Sign the paper.
常言说得好  老婆开心
Know what they say: "Happy wife,
日子舒心
happy life."
开吃吧
Let's eat.
二  三  八  四  六
Two, three, eight, four, six.
谢尔顿已经背到π的小数点后第20位
3. 14159 26535 89793 23846
再说就要吐了
That's all I can do without throwing up.
我可没料到
That is not what I expected
你说打嗝说出π[馅饼]是这个意思
when you said you were gonna burp "Pie."
刚有人说"馅饼"吗
Did somebody say "Pie"?!
我不知道哪种更吓人
I don't know what's scarier:
厕所小丑
the bathroom clowns
还是把小丑放进去的女人
or the woman that put them there.
我只知道  车上只能放下一个她
All I know is you can only fit one of her in a car.
那是从她身体里蹦出来的小丑
And there's the clown that came out of her.
我之前真的不想来
I really didn't want to come here,
但看来这次感恩节
but this is shaping up to be
是我多年以来过得最开心的一次
one of the best Thanksgivings I've had in a long time.
我也是
Me, too.
喂  华仔说你们一整天都在取笑他
Hey. Howie says you've been making fun of him all day!
现在你们两个马上道歉
Now, both of you apologize right now!
她个子好小啊
She's so tiny.
她生气的样子好好笑
It's funny when she's mad.
小伙子
All right, mister,
我想你应该向霍华德和伯纳黛特道歉
I think you owe Howard and Bernadette an apology.
也许你是对的
Perhaps you're right.
我为我的行为道歉
I'm sorry for my behavior.
我摄入了酒精  导致我行为不当
I've had alcohol, and it's caused me to be inappropriate.
-没事  -没关系
- It's okay. - Don't worry about it.
谢谢
Thank you.
她是不是好贤惠
Ain't she great?
谢尔顿
Sheldon.
快去给老爷们儿拿啤酒吧
Now, how's about you get us a couple of beers?
再次感谢你下厨
Thanks again for cooking.
所有菜都超级好吃
Yeah, everything was delicious.
没我最喜欢的两个女生帮忙  我也做不到啊
Well, I couldn't have done it without my two favorite girls.
玛莎·斯图尔特和瑞秋·雷[厨艺天后]
Martha Stewart and Rachael Ray.
谢尔顿  我们出去
Hey, Sheldon, what do you say we go outside
玩下橄榄球如何[猪皮]
and throw around the old pigskin?
这家是犹太人
This is a Jewish house.
我想他们没猪皮
I don't think they have pigskin.
刚有人说"猪皮"吗
Did someone say pigskin!
亲爱的  今天的事很抱歉
Hey, honey, I'm sorry about today.
我保证  下次结婚
And I promise, next time I get married,
绝对不会是闹着玩
it won't be a joke.
一定是为了爱
It'll be for love.
或是钱
Or money.
我也抱歉
I'm sorry, too.
别这样
Don't be.
都是我的错
It's my fault.
我是个糟糕的老公
I was a terrible husband.
从未陪在老婆身边
I was never around.
我知道我对你太严厉了
I know I'm hard on you,
但你不是世界上最差劲的女婿
but you're not the worst son-in-law in the world.
迈克  这是你对我说过的最贴心的话
Mike, that's the nicest thing you've ever said to me.
我喝醉了
Well, I'm drunk.
我刚刚吐在了很多小丑身上
I just vomited on a lot of clowns.